<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post | gyninfo.eu</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Post</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Post</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>AIM</title>
      <link>/post/aim/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/aim/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2020-07-08-aim.en_files/reproductive-health-supplies-coalition-Is-oKcKl7d0-unsplash.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; height=&#34;200&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aim of this site is to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide up-to-date scientifically based information in the specialty of Obstetrics &amp;amp; Gynaecology, within our expert fields.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;offer access to scientific information in a form readable for also non-doctors&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;express our opinion on actual issues – called “editorials”&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;give access to presentations made by our staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The information is indexed according to the index below&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;scope&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Scope&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The access to rapid and often free information within any field has expanded rapidly by time. During the latest decade, however, in many areas, ideological issues increasingly influence the selection of information presented, with the consequence that even professionals sometimes apparently live in “different worlds”.&lt;br /&gt;
We all know that nobody can be 100% objective. Our way strive for objectivity is based on three principles: No commercials on this site. None of us are engaged in boards of pharmaceutical companies, and none of us have shares in industry. This is of course no guaranty of objectivity, like people who have such engagements may be fully objective. But nevertheless.
We also attempt to go beyond apparently conflicting results in different studies on the same topic, and to do better than just to declare: We can draw no conclusion, as different studies emerge with different results. Our experience tell us, at usually, one might explain the apparently different results. Good studies generally provide more reliable results than poor studies.&lt;br /&gt;
In order to make the information on this site relevant for clinically working people, all who are presenting information on this site are clinically working colleagues (part-time or fulltime).
Finally, we encourage colleagues who want to share useful information and at the same time fulfill our principles outlined, to send us such information. We have full right to refuse such an upload, but will be happy to do so, if we find the information useful.&lt;br /&gt;
So, please enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;index&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;INDEX&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The information is indexed according to the following headlines:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short- and long-term health issues with use of hormonal contraception&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use of hormonal contraception in Denmark / Scandinavia&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hormonal contraception and risk of venous thrombosis&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hormonal contraception and risk of arterial thrombosis&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hormonal contraception and risk of breast cancer risk&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hormonal contraception and risk of ovarian cancer&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hormonal contraception and risk of endometrial cancer&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hormonal contraception and risk of colo-rectal cancer&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hormonal contraception and risk of depression/suicides&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hormonal contraception; clinical notes&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frequent questions and our answers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hormone therapy and cancer risk&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How does different types of hormones influence the risk of different female cancers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miscarriages&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The frequency of miscarriages in Denmark through 40 years.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reproductive prognosis after pregnancy losses&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associations between miscarriages and future health in mothers&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frequent question and our answers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Induced abortion&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medically and surgically induced abortion in Denmark 2000-2019&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Early pregnancy national quality assessment in Denmark (Tigrab.dk)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1st trimester medically induced abortion&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2nd trimester medically induced abortion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frequent question and our answers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Post-term birth-induction and stillbirth risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
